<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blogs on Faraz Akhtar</title><link>http://frzkhtr.github.io/blogs/</link><description>Recent content in Blogs on Faraz Akhtar</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 22:00:50 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://frzkhtr.github.io/blogs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>------------Blogs Coming soon | Stay Tuned---------</title><link>http://frzkhtr.github.io/blogs/first_post/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 22:00:50 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://frzkhtr.github.io/blogs/first_post/</guid><description>I am excited to announce that next month, I will be releasing a blog on the topic of &amp;ldquo;Judgment under Uncertainty: Heuristics and Biases.&amp;rdquo; This blog will delve into the research conducted by Nobel Prize-winning psychologists Daniel Kahneman and Amos Tversky, who identified various cognitive biases that affect our decision-making processes. I will explore how these biases can lead to errors in judgment, both in everyday life and in more significant contexts such as politics and finance.</description></item><item><title>------------My Journey of Building a Custom PC: Tips, Tricks and Lessons Learned---------</title><link>http://frzkhtr.github.io/blogs/pc_building/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 21:35:50 +0530</pubDate><guid>http://frzkhtr.github.io/blogs/pc_building/</guid><description>Building a custom PC from scratch can be a daunting task, especially if you are not familiar with the process. However, with the right tools, guidance, and patience, it can be a rewarding experience. In this blog, I will share my personal journey of building a custom PC, along with some tips, tricks, and lessons learned.
First, I had to decide on the parts I wanted for my PC. I did some research online and consulted with friends who had built their own computers.</description></item></channel></rss>